Hello everyone, this is Takaichi Ho.
I am Tomoko Hazuki.
I am Aoba Mori.
Yes, that means,
That's not what I mean.
So, what a surprise that these three of us are going to have a dialogue this time.
The three of us will be performing at Tokyo Night Land vol. 4 on December 5.
Tokyo Night Land vol. 4, which will be held on December 5,
Before that, we would like to have a talk with these three old friends.
I would like to talk about various topics with these three old friends of mine.
Oh no, I bit my tongue right from the start!
I also had a bit of a moment when I said my own name. I was like...
I was told before we started that it would be fine to have a reunion-like atmosphere, but...
But it was a little bit different, wasn't it?
I was nervous.
Yes, we are going to perform in Tokyu Night Land.
This is the first time for the three of us to be on stage together.
It's the first time.
No, no, no, no.
It's been a while.
We've just started rehearsals.
I've seen the two of you singing and dancing before, so it's new for me to see you acting.
So it's new for me to see them acting.
That's true.
It's fresh, isn't it?
How do you like it? There's a lot of laughter this time.
We're having a lot of fun during the rehearsals.
We come up with ideas together.
We're trying our best to come up with ideas that would be funnier this way.
I can't tell you yet because it would be a spoiler. I can't tell you yet because it would be a spoiler.
It's a little bit like a duo.
It's something that can only come out of a long-time relationship.
It's something you can only get from a long-time friend.
It's cool.
I can see the bond between us.
We share the same birthday.
We have the same birthday.
It's amazing, isn't it?
It's our birthday.
But we don't get to see each other often.
It's been a while since I've seen Chi-chan and Tomo.
They thought I was Tomochan.
I guess we've all become beautiful older women on the outside
But on the inside...
It's a relief to know that we're all still the same... and that we haven't seen each other for as long as we did.
But everyone's still the same... but... this nighttime land... is full of idols.
I was a little nervous and anxious because there were a lot of Stardust idols in the show, so having three people who know each other's faces made me feel more at ease.
You know...
It makes me want to work harder.
But we've all performed on stage before, right?
You know, they've all appeared on stage before, right?
You see them on social media, and you see them in roles like this, and you see them in visuals like this, but...
But I haven't been able to ask you what it was like in real life.
I'd be interested to hear about it.
I've been participating in events recently, mainly on stage.
I was in a play called "Maji de Tokimeke Shoujo-tachi" (Girls Who Can't Wait) the other day.
It's a story about a battle between schools in a fictional sporting event.
Our school is the bad guy, and we do bad things.
Evil? Evil?
I was supposed to be evil or something.
But he played it exactly the same way, like he didn't want to be played.
I don't think so.
I think he's more than just a problem child.
It's more like he just stared at me like this the whole time.
Ew.
I think his eyes would roll back into his head if he were to do the play.
I've been doing this kind of staring every day.
I've been doing that recently.
What do they say?
What do your fans say? Like, from fans?
Either you had a fresh, I don't know, I've never seen anything like it, or you were into it in a good way, not quite as it was, but in a good way.
I thought he looked great as a villain,
It was a compliment, a compliment.
I thought you were perfect for that kind of role.
I don't know if you remember.
I want to play a villain.
Have you done it yet? How about recently?
I played the opposite of evil, I think.
But first of all, the first play I ever performed in was
The curtain rises, which is a movie that our seniors, Momochiro Clover Z, had done in the past,
It was a work that really meant a lot to me,
And the three of us, actually,
I was an extra in Garu's film for a little bit,
I had a small part in Garu as an extra, so I was very surprised that I could be a part of it,
I played the role of Garuru, and Rimi Takagi, who played the role of Garuru in the movie, also played the role of Garuru,
Rimi Takagi, who played the role of Garuru in the movie, told me that Chi-chan was going to play the role,
I was very happy to hear that, and I was also happy to hear that she was going to play the role of Garuru,
I was not exactly the opposite of myself, but when I read the script, I thought that I wouldn't have said that, I was not exactly the opposite of myself, but when I read the script, there were many things I would not have said or done,
It took me a long time to empathize with them one by one,
It took me a long time to empathize with them one by one. I was amazed at how hard it is for everyone to create a role, and how amazing it is.
So I learned a lot from them.
How about you, Tomo-chan?
This year, I am playing a role in a play called "Lys Noir" in June, which is about magic,
I played the role of a teacher in the Herbology Department,
I played a taciturn role, so I was basically emotionless,
I was protecting the students.
A teacher? I felt like a teacher.
Yes, I feel like a big sister.
Like a teacher. But I did a play based on the Shinsengumi a few years ago, and I played the role of a female swordsman,
At that time, I played the role of a female swordsman, so I had a little bit of a role in that, but now I've been asked to play a role in this Shinsengumi,
I love it! It's my favorite Shinsengumi story! There is a senior member of the Shinsengumi!
I'm a little bit curious about the story of the Shinsengumi,
What about your personal life? Recently?
Private?
Well, I don't know if I'd go so far as to call it "Jinsui", but I mean, you know, on stage, there's a lot of rehearsal every day.
You've been rehearsing every day, right? Yes. And since we work from morning till night, I wanted to eat a lot of food, so I used to buy lunch.
But I thought, well, I don't want to buy something every day, and I thought, well, I've been saying I'm going to do jitsu-mizu, and I've been doing it for about three or five years, and I thought, well, this can only mean one thing.
I'm a little bit withdrawn, so don't do it. I'm pulling back a little bit, stop.
I'm pulling back a little bit, stop.
You mean you said that?
I'm making sweet potatoes at night.
Oh, you mean that?
Sweet potatoes. I was cursing.
Are you okay? I don't think they're going to come out.
I don't want to take the sweet potatoes with me, you know,
So I washed, cut, and boiled the sweet potatoes,
And then just take it and go. Take it as is, crisp.
It looks cheap.
It fills me up so much, and I feel like I'm going to spend a lot of time on it,
I feel like I have a lot of power over time,
I really recommend it for stage rehearsals or when you want a hearty meal.
Sweet potatoes.
If you have the courage to eat a little,
It's delicious, really. You can eat it without seasoning.
My grandpa likes sweet potatoes.
But then I saw on Instagram that he was making homemade food,
Wow, he's too good at cooking.
Oh, no. I'd be embarrassed if Chomo told me.
You can cook, right?
She made a really delicious-looking dish. She recommends it.
How are you doing lately? I'm playing games all the time. I play games too.
I play APEX all the time. I'm not very good at it yet.
Are you a good gamer? You know, the kind of games people play in real life.
I've been trying hard with headphones on, but I can't get a hit at all.
What's not hitting?
I can't hit the target and I can't beat it,
I'm addicted to it, and I play it all night long.
I was thinking of Chomo reading a book at the local library.
That's the image I had of you.
I've been playing Splatoon for a long time.
I've been playing Splatoon my whole life.
But I did play Splatoon for a while. I did, you know. Everyone goes through Splatoon.
That's how we are. That's how we spend our private time.
So, we've talked about a lot of things, and tomorrow, the three of us will continue to talk about them.
So, please watch for the next installment.
So far, I have been talking with Ho Koichi, Tamako Hazuki, and Aoba Mori. So far my partners have been Ho Koichi, Tamako Hazuki, and Aoba Mori.
Bye-bye!
Bye bye!
Yakanto Idol